WZD	ENG	FRE	SPA

TITLE_WZD	Initial Setup	Installation initiale	Configuración inicial

TITLE_WLC	Welcome	Bienvenue	Bienvenido

TITLE_VIZIO	VIZIO\nConnected TV	VIZIO\nTéléviseur connecté	VIZIO\nTV conectada

TITLE_INTERNET	Connect to\nthe Internet	Se connecter\n à Internet	Conectar\n al Internet

DESC_WLC	Allow the VIZIO Setup Wizard to help you tune your channels.	Permettre à l'assistant d'installation de VIZIO de vous aider à régler vos chaînes.	Deje que el Asistente de configuración VIZIO le ayude a sintonizar los canales.

TITLE_LANG	Change\nLanguage	Changement\nde langue	Cambiar\nidioma

DESC_LANG	Please select your language:	Veuillez choisir votre langue:	Seleccione su idioma:

LANG_1	English	Anglais	English

LANG_2	French	Français	Français

LANG_3	Spanish	Espagnol	Español

TITLE_TUNER	Set up Your \nTV Signal 	Configuration \nsignal TV	Configurar señal \nde su TV

DESC_TUNER	How are you receiving your TV service?	Qualité réception TV ?	¿Cómo recibe su servicio de TV?

TUNER_1	Antenna	Antenne	Antena

TUNER_2	Cable	Câble	Cable

TUNER_3	Satellite	Satellite	Satélite

TITLE_SCAN	Channel Scan	Balayage des canaux	Escaneo de canales

DESC_SCAN	Please connect your cable or antenna to the DTV/TV input	Conecte el cable o la antena a la entrada DTV/TV	Veuillez brancher votre câble ou votre antenne sur l'entrée DTV/TV

SCAN_1	Scan	Balayage	Escanear

SCAN_2	Skip Scan	Sauter des balayage	Saltar escanear

SCAN_HEAD	Channel Scan will take a few minutes to complete.\n\n	Le balayage de chaînes peut prendre un certain temps.\n\n	La búsqueda de canales puede tardar un poco en completarse.\n\n

SCAN_PROGRESS	Status: Scanning	État: Balayage	Estado: Buscando

SCAN_COMPLETE	Status: Scan Complete	État: Balayage terminé	Estado: Búsqueda completada

SCAN_CANCEL	Status: Scan Cancel	État: Annulation du balayage	Estado: Búsqueda cancelada

SCAN_ERROR	Status: Scan Error	État: Erreur de balayage	Estado: Error de búsqueda

SCAN_ANLG_CH	Analog Channels: 	Chaînes analogiques: 	Canales analógicos: 

SCAN_DIG_CH	Digital Channels: 	Chaînes numériques: 	Canales digitales: 

TITLE_CMPL	Set Up\nComplete	Configuration\nterminée	Configuración\nTerminada

DESC_CMPL	Congratulations. Set up is complete!	Bravo. Configuration terminée !	¡Configuración Terminada!

HELP_BACK	Back	Retour	Volver

HELP_HELP	Help	Aide	Ayuda

HELP_SKIP	Skip	Passer	Omitir

HELP_SELECT	Select	Choisi	Selecto

HELP_ENTER	Next	Suivant	Siguiente

HELP_EXIT	Exit	Sortie	Salida

HELP_CANCEL	Cancel	Annulez	Cancelar

HELP_LAN	Language	Langue	Idioma

HELP_RETAIL	Retail Mode	Mode Magasin	Modo para Casa

EMPTY			

DESC_TIME_ZONE	Please select your time zone:	Sélectionnez votre Fuseau Horaire:	"Por favor, seleccione su Zona Horaria:"

TITLE_ENERGY_STAR	Change\nLocation	Changement\nde lieu	Cambiar\nubicación

DESC_ENERGY_STAR	Please select Home mode when installing this TV in your home	Sélect Maison si instal. chez vous	Usar Modo hogar en casa.

ENERGY_STAR	Home Mode Setup	Mode de Maison	Configurar Modo de Casa

ENERGY_STAR_0	Store Demo	Mode de Magasin	Demo  de Tienda

ENERGY_STAR_1	Begin Activation	Commencez I'activation	Empezar activación

ENERGY_STAR_2	Retail Mode	Mode Magasin	Modo para Tienda

ENERGY_STAR_3	Switch to Home Mode	Passer en mode Domicile	Cambiar al Modo para Casa

ENERGY_STAR_4	Use Retail Mode	Utiliser  le mode Magasin	Usar Modo para Tienda

ENERGY_STAR_INFO	This is for retail display only and is not meant for home use. Are you sure you want to enter the Store Demo Mode?	Il s'agit pour l'affichage au magasin et n'est pas destiné à un usage domestique. Êtes-vous sûr de vouloir entrer dans le Demo du Magasin?	Esto es para uso en tienda solamente y no intencionado para uso domestico?

TITLE_TIME_ZONE	Change\nTimeZone	Changement\nfuseau horaire	Cambiar\nzona horaria

TIME_ZONE_EAS	Eastern	Côte Est	Este

TIME_ZONE_IND	Indiana	Indiana	Indiana

TIME_ZONE_CEN	Central	Central	Centro

TIME_ZONE_MNT	Mountain	Rocheuses	Montaña

TIME_ZONE_ARI	Arizona	Arizona	Arizona

TIME_ZONE_PAC	Pacific	Pacifique	Pacífico

TIME_ZONE_ALA	Alaska	Alaska	Alaska

TIME_ZONE_HAW	Hawaii	Hawaii	Hawai

TIME_ZONE_ATLA	Atlantic	Atlantique	Atlántico

TIME_ZONE_NFL	Newfoundland	Terre-Neuve	Terranova

TITLE_DST	Change\nDaylight Saving	Changement\nhoraire été	Cambiar horario\nde verano

DST_OFF	Off	Arrêt	Agapado

DST_ON	On	Activé	Activado

SETUP_PROGRESS	SET-UP PROGRESS	AVANCEMENT CONFIGURATION	PROGRESO DE CONFIGURACIÓN

MSG_SIGNAL_CHOOSE	Choose signal	Choix signal	Elija señal

MSG_SCAN_BEGIN	Begin Scan	Début du Balayage	Comenzar Escaneo

MSG_SCAN_STOP	Stop Scan	Arrêtez le Balayage	Detenga la Búsqueda

MSG_EXIT	Exit to Live TV	Quitter pour TV direct	Salir a TV en vivo

ANNOUNCE_TEXT	Make sure your cable is connected from the wall to the TV then start the channel scan.	"Assurez-vous que le câble est bien connecté entre le mur et la télévision, puis commencez le balayage des chaînes."	"Asegúrese de que su señal de cable esté conectada de la pared al TV, y luego comience el escaneo de canales."

ANNOUNCE_TEXT_ANT	Make sure your cable is connected from the antenna to the TV then start the channel scan.	"Assurez-vous que le câble est bien connecté entre l'antenne et la télévision, puis commencez le balayage des chaînes."	"Asegúrese de que su señal de cable esté conectada de la antena al TV, y luego comience el escaneo de canales."

ANNOUNCE_TEXT_CAB	Make sure your cable is connected from the cable box to the TV then start the channel scan. 	"Assurez-vous que le câble est bien connecté entre le décodeur et la télévision, puis commencez le balayage des chaînes."	"Asegúrese de que su señal de cable esté conectada de la caja de cable al TV, y luego comience el escaneo de canales."

ANNOUNCE_TEXT_SAT	Make sure your cable is connected from the satellite box to the TV then start the channel scan.	"Assurez-vous que le câble est bien connecté entre la boîte satellite et la télévision, puis commencez le balayage des chaînes."	"Asegúrese de que su señal de cable esté conectada de la caja de satélite al TV, y luego comience el escaneo de canales."

ANNOUNCE_TEXT_WALL	Make sure your cable is connected from the wall to the TV then start the channel scan.	"Assurez-vous que le câble est bien connecté entre le mur et la télévision, puis commencez le balayage des chaînes."	"Asegúrese de que su señal de cable esté conectada de la pared al TV, y luego comience el escaneo de canales."

ANNOUNCE_TEXT_SATE	Make sure your cable is connected from the satellite box to the TV then start the channel scan.	Make sure your cable is connected from the satellite box to the TV and start the channel scan below.	Make sure your cable is connected from the satellite box to the TV and start the channel scan below.

DLG_YES	Yes	Oui	Sí

DLG_NO	No	Non	No

DLG_OK	OK	OK	Aceptar

DLG_GO_BACK	Go Back	retournez	Regresar

MSG_SAVE	Save	enregistrer	Guardar

MSG_NAME_THIS_INPUT	Name this input	Nommez cette entrée	Nombrar esta entrada

MSG_PRESS_OK_TO_CHOOSE	<Press OK to choose>	<Pressez OK>	<Presione OK >

MSG_PROMPT_DLG_TEXT	"If you do not set up your tuner, you will not able to watch your favorite channels. Are you sure you want to skip this step?"	Si vous n'installez pas votre tuner. vous pas capable observer vos canaux préférés. Êtes-vous sûr vous voulez-vous sauter cette étape ?	"Si no configura el sintonizador,  usted no podra ver sus canales favoritos. ¿Está seguro que desea omitir este paso?"

NETWORK_COPYRIGHT_TITLE	You must accept the Terms of Service and Privacy Policy to activate the Internet functionality.	Vous devez accepter les limites du service et de la politique en matière de protection de la vie privée pour activer la fonctionnalité d'Internet.	"Para activar la funcionalidid de Internet, debera aceptar los Terminos de Servicio y la Politica de Privacidad"

NETWORK_TERMS_TEXT	Click here to read the Yahoo! Connected TV Term of Service.	Cliquez ici pour lire le mandat du Service de Yahoo! TV connecté.	Haga clic aquí para leer los Términos de Servicio de Yahoo! Connected TV.

NETWORK_TERMS_CB	I accept the Terms of Service.	J'accepte les Limites du Service.	Acepto los Terminos de Servicio.

NETWORK_PRIVACY_TEXT	Click here to read the Yahoo! Connected TV Privacy Policy.	Cliquez ici pour lire la politique de confidentialité de Yahoo! TV connecté.	Haga clic aqui para leer la Politica de Privacidad de Yahoo! Connected TV.

NETWORK_PRIVACY_CB	I accept the Privacy Policy.	J'accepte la clause de confidentialité.	Acepto la Politica de Privacidad.

NETWORK_TOS_BACK	Back	Retour	Atrás

NETWORK_ROUTER_LIST_TITLE	You can connect to the Internet through a wired (Ethernet) connection or select from the available wireless networks below to use the built-in wireless functionality. 	Vous pouvez vous connecter à Internet via une connexion filaire (Ethernet) ou sans fil intégrée fonctionnellement.	Puede conectarse al Internet a mediante una conexion con cable (Ethernet) o la funcion integrada inalambrica.

NETWORK_ROUTER_LIST_LIST_TITLE	Available wireless networks	Réseaux sans fil disponibles	Reds inalambricas disponibles

NETWORK_ROUTER_LIST_SEARCHING	Searching for network signal...	Recherche du signal du réseau ...	Buscando señal de red

NETWORK_ROUTER_LIST_SSID	Manually Enter Network Name (SSID)	Entrée manuelle de nom de réseau (SSID)	Entre manualmente nombre de red (SSID)

NETWORK_ROUTER_LIST_WIRED	Connect Using an Ethernet Cable	Se connecter en utilisant un câble Ethernet	Conectar utilizando un cable de Ethernet

NETWORK_ROUTER_UNABLE_CONNECT	Unable to establish a network connection. Please try again.	Impossible d'établir une connexion réseau. S'il vous plaît essayez de nouveau.	"No se puede establer una conexion de red. Por favor, inténtelo de nuevo."

NETWORK_ROUTER_CONNECTING	Attempting to join network…	Tenter de rejoindre le réseau ...	Intentando unirse a la red…

NETWORK_PWD_TITLE	"The selected wireless network requires a security code that can be entered by soft keypad (press OK). If you do not remember the code, please refer to the user manual for the router, or contact the router manufacturer."	"Le réseau sans fil sélectionné nécessite un code de sécurité qui peuvent être enterd par clavier souple (pressez OK). Si vous ne me souviens pas du code. S'il vous plaît se référer au manuel utilisateur pour le routeur, ou contactez le fabricant du routeur."	"La red inalámbrica seleccionada requiere un código de seguridad que se puede introducir por teclado suave (pulse OK). Si no recuerda el código, por favor consulte el manual del usuario del router, o en contacto con el fabricante del enrutador."

NETWORK_PWD_CODE	Code	Code	Codigo  

NETWORK_PWD_CONNECT	Connect	Connectez	Conectar

NETWORK_PWD_WIRED_TITLE	You can choose a wired connection by connecting an Ethernet cable to the back of the TV.	Vous pouvez choisir une connexion filaire en connectant un câble Ethernet à l'arrière du téléviseur.	Usted puede elegir la conexion cableada por mediante de conectar un cable de Ethernet por la parte posterior del televisor.

NETWORK_PWD_SSID	SSID	SSID	SSID

NETWORK_PWD_KEY	Key	Clés	Clave

NETWORK_PWD_CONNECT_FAIL	Connection failed. Please check your password and try again.	Échec de la connexion. S'il vous plaît vérifier votre mot de passe et essayez à nouveau.	"Error de conexion. Por favor, compruebe su contraseña y intente de nuevo."

NETWORK_NEXT_TITLE	The Internet connection is active but slow which can impact some VIA services such as streaming video quality. This can be caused by your router or broadband service level. To maximize your online experience please upgrade your router or internet service speed.	"La connexion Internet est active, mais lente, qui peut influer sur certains services de VIA tels que le streaming vidéo de qualité. Cela peut être causé par votre niveau de service routeur ou à large bande. Afin de maximiser votre expérience en ligne s'il vous plaît mettre à jour votre routeur ou de la vitesse du service Internet."	"La conexión de Internet está activa, pero lento, que puede afectar algunos de los servicios de VIA, como la calidad de video cuando streaming. Esto puede ser causado por su nivel de servicio o router de banda ancha. Para maximizar su experiencia en línea por favor actualice su router o de servicio de Internet."

NETWORK_NEXT_NEXT	Next	Suivant	Siguiente

NETWORK_WIRED_NEXT_TITLE	Wired connection detected. Testing the network…	Connexion filaire détectés. Test du réseau ...	Conexion de cable detectado. Pruebe la red….

NETWORK_WIRELESS_NEXT_TITLE	The wireless network connection is active and is being tested...	La connexion au réseau sans fil est active et est à l'essai ...	La conexión de red inalámbrica está activa y se está probando …

NETWORK_NEXT_WIRED_HELP	The wired connection may provide better performance.	La connexion filaire peut offrir de meilleures performances.	La conexión por cable pueden ofrecer un mejor rendimiento.

NETWORK_REG_INFO_TITLE	REGISTER YOUR TV	ENREGISTREZ LE TELEVISEUR	REGISTRAR EL TELEVISOR

NETWORK_REG_INFO_EMAIL	Enter E-mail	Entrez l'E-mail	Ingrese E-mail

NETWORK_REG_INFO_FIRST_NAME	Enter First Name	Entrez le Prénom	Ingrese Nombre

NETWORK_REG_INFO_LAST_NAME	Enter Last Name	Entrez le Nom de Famille	Ingrese Apellido

NETWORK_REG_INFO_PHONE_NUM	Enter Phone Number	Entrez le Numéro de Téléphone	Ingrese Número de Teléfono

NETWORK_REG_INFO_ZIP	Enter ZIP Code	Entrez le Code Postal	Ingrese Código Postal

NETWORK_REG_INFO_EMAIL_DLG_TXT	The E-mail has an error. Try again. 	Le l'E-mail a une erreur. Veuillez réessayer. 	El E-mail tiene un error. Intente de nuevo. 

NETWORK_REG_INFO_FIRST_NAME_DLG_TXT	The First Name has an error. Try again. 	Le Prénom a une erreur. Veuillez réessayer. 	El Nombre tiene un error. Intente de nuevo. 

NETWORK_REG_INFO_LAST_NAME_DLG_TXT	The Last Name has an error. Try again. 	Le Nom de Famille a une erreur. Veuillez réessayer. 	El Apellido tiene un error. Intente de nuevo. 

NETWORK_REG_INFO_PHONE_NUM_DLG_TXT	The Phone Number has an error. Try again. 	Le Numéro de Téléphone a une erreur. Veuillez réessayer. 	El Número de Teléfono tiene un error. Intente de nuevo. 

NETWORK_REG_INFO_ZIP_DLG_TXT	The ZIP Code has an error. Try again. 	Le Code Postal a une erreur. Veuillez réessayer. 	El Código Postal tiene un error. Intente de nuevo. 

NETWORK_REG_INFO_EMAIL_ACCEPT	"Yes, email me VIZIO product info and special offers."	"Oui, envoyez-moi les infos produits VIZIO et les offres spéciales."	"Sí, envíeme por correo electrónico la información del producto VIZIO y ofertas especiales."

NETWORK_REG_INFO_WEB_ADDS	View the VIZIO Privacy Policy at www.vizio.com/privacy	Consultez la Politique de Confidentialité de VIZIO sur www.vizio.com/privacy	Ver la Política de Privacidad VIZIO en www.vizio.com/privacy

NETWORK_REG_INFO_DLG_MSG	Are you sure you want to skip registration?	Etes-vous certain de vouloir éviter l’inscription ?	¿Está seguro que quiere omitir el registro?

NETWORK_REG_INFO_DLG_BACK	Back	Retour	Atrás

NETWORK_REG_INFO_DLG_SKIP	Skip	Passer	Omitir

NETWORK_REG_INFO_BTN_NEXT	Next	Suivant	Siguiente

NETWORK_REG_INFO_BTN_SKIP	Skip	Passer	Omitir

NETWORK_SKIP_PROMPT_TEXT	Are you sure you want to skip Wi-Fi Network?	Etes-vous certain de vouloir éviter la connexion au réseau Wi-Fi ?	¿Está seguro que quiere omitir la red Wi-Fi?

NETWORK_SKIP_PROMPT_TEXT_TOS	Are you sure you want to skip Terms of Service?	Etes-vous certain de vouloir éviter les Conditions d'Utilisation ?	¿Está seguro que quiere omitir el Términos de Servicio?

NETWORK_SKIP_PROMPT_TEXT_DESC	"You will not be able to access premium movies, shows, music and online applications from the Internet."	"Vous ne pourrez pas accéder à des films de la meilleure qualité, à des expositions, à la musique et à des programmes d'application temps réel de l'Internet."	"Usted no podrá tener acceso a películas de primera, programas, música y las aplicaciones en línea por Internet."

NETWORK_NO_CONNECT_TITLE	Neither a wired or wireless connection was detected.	Ni un raccordement de câble ou sans fil a été détecté.	Ni una conexión cableada o inalámbrica se ha detectado.

NETWORK_NO_CONNECT_AGAIN_WARN	"Please verify that the router is on and functioning properly, then search again."	"Veuillez vérifier que le routeur est en ligne et fonctionnant correctement, puis recherche encore."	"Por favor de verificar si el router esta encendido y funcionando correctamente, y despues intente la busqueda de nuevo. "

NETWORK_NO_CONNECT_MANU_WARN	"If you know the wireless network name (SSID), enter it manually."	"Si vous savez le nom de réseau sans fil (SSID), écrivez-le manuellement."	"Si conoce el nombre de red inalambrica (SSID), entrela manualmente"

NETWORK_NO_CONNECT_AGAIN_BTN	Search Again for Wireless Networks	Recherche encore des réseaux sans fil	Buscar redes inalambricas de nuevo. 

NETWORK_PROMPT_DLG_MSG	"If you do not set up your network, you will not be able to access premium movies, shows, music and online applications from the Internet. Are you sure you want to skip this step?"	"Si vous n'installez pas votre réseau, vous ne pourrez pas accéder à des films de la meilleure qualité, à des expositions, à la musique et à des programmes d'application temps réel de l'Internet. Êtes-vous sûr vous voulez-vous sauter cette étape ?"	"Usted no podra tener acceso a películas de primera, programas, musica, y las aplicaciones en línea por Internet. Esta seguro que desea omitir este paso? "

NETWORK_PWS_TIT_WPA2	Please enter your WPA2 Passphrase	Entrez votre phrase secrète WPA2	Ingrese su frase de seguridad WPA2

NETWORK_PWS_TIT_WPA	Please enter your WPA Passphrase	Entrez votre phrase secrète WPA	Ingrese su frase de seguridad WPA

NETWORK_PWS_TIT_WEP	Enter WEP Passphrase	Saisir Phrase de passe WEP	Introducir Frase de contraseña WEP

LOC_DESC_TITLE	Getting Started	Mise en route	Para empezar

LOC_DESC_TEXT	"Insert the provided batteries into the remote control and use the UP %p, DOWN %p and OK buttons to navigate the set-up screens."	"Insérez les piles fournies dans la télécommande et d'utiliser le UP %p, BAS %p et OK pour naviguer dans les écrans de paramétrage."	"Inserte las baterias en el control y use los botones Arriba %p, Abajo %p y OK para navegar por las pantallas de configuracion."

NETWORK_VKB_NEXT	Next Entry	Prochaine entrée	Siguente entrada

NETWORK_VKB_CANCEL	Cancel	Annulez	Cancelar

BT_REMOTE_CONTROL_TITLE	Activate the Remote Control	Activez l'à télécommande	Activar el control remoto

BT_REMOTE_SEARCH_DESC	Searching for your remote control...	Recherche votre à télécommande…	En busca de su control remoto

BT_REMOTE_SEARCH_DESC_TEXT	HOLD DOWN RECORD AND GREEN KEYS	MAINTENEZ ENFONCÉES LES TOUCHES ENREGISTRER ET VERTE	MANTENER OPRIMIDAS LAS TECLAS GRABAR Y VERDE

BT_REMOTE_SEARHING	Please wait	Attendez svp	"Por favor, espere"

BT_REMOTE_NOT_FOUND_DESC	The remote control was not found.	La télécommande n'a pas été trouvée.	El control remoto no fue encontrado.

BT_REMOTE_NOT_FOUND_TIP	"Simultaneously hold down the Record %p button and Green %p button for five seconds, and then select ""Let's Try Again""."	"Appuyez simultanément sur le %p bouton Enregistrer et Vert %p raccourci pendant cinq secondes, puis sélectionnez ""Essai laissé encore""."	"Simultaniamente mantenga oprimido el %p boton de Grabacion %p y del acceso direct Verde por 5 segundos, y luego seleccione ""Intentar de Nuevo""."

BT_REMOTE_TRY_AGAIN	Let's Try Again	Essai laissé encore	Intentar de Nuevo

BT_REMOTE_FOUND_DESC	 %p  REMOTE FOUND	 %p  TÉLÉCOMMANDE TROUVÉE	 %p  CONTROL REMOTO ENCONTRADO

BT_REMOTE_FOUND	Connect to the Internet	Se connecter à Internet	Conectar al Internet

BT_REMOTE_FOUND_TIP	"Access premium movies, shows, music and online applications by connecting your TV to the Internet."	"Accédez aux films de la meilleure qualité, aux expositions, à la musique et aux programmes d'application temps réel en reliant votre TV à l'Internet."	"Acceso a películas de estreno, espectáculos, música y aplicaciones en línea mediante la conexión de su TV a la Internet."

BT_REMOTE_PROMPT_DLG_TEXT	Are you sure you want to skip this step? The advanced features of your remote control will not be functional.	Êtes-vous sûr vous voulez-vous sauter cette étape ? Les dispositifs avancés de votre à télécommande ne seront pas fonctionnels.	¿Está seguro que desea omitir este paso? Las funciones avanzadas de su remoto no funcionaran.

BT_REMOTE_DLG_RETRY	Retry	Retour	Volver

BT_REMOTE_DLG_SKIP	Skip	Passer	Omitir

TITLE_DEVICE	Set Up Your\nDevices	Installez vos dispositifs	Configurar sus\nDispositivos

DESC_DEVICE	Set up your device by selecting it from the menu below.	Installez votre dispositif en le choisissant à partir du menu ci-dessous.	Configure su dispositivo a mediante seleccionandolo en el menu de abajo. 

DEVICE_CHOOSE_DEVICE	Choose Device	Choisissez le Dispositif	Elegir Dispositivos

DEVICE_SEL_BRAND	Select Brand	Choisissez la Marque	Seleccionar Marca

DEVICE_SEL_MODEL	Select Model	Choisissez la Modèle	Seleccionar Modelo

DEVICE_SEL_INPUT	Select Input	Sélection de L'entrée	Seleccionar Entrada

DEVICE_CONTINUE	 Continue	 Continuez	 Continuar

DEVICE_CHK_CONN	Please check your connections if you do not see video or hear audio from the device.	"S'il vous plaît vérifiez vos connexions, si vous ne voyez pas la vidéo ou écouter le son de l'appareil."	"Por favor, revise sus conexiones si no ve video o escucha audio del dispositivo. "

DEVICE_TURN_ON_DEVICE	Make sure the device is turned on and connected to the input you selected.	Assurez-vous que l'appareil est allumé et connecté à l'entrée que vous avez sélectionné.	Asegure de que el dispositivo este encendido  y conectado a la entrada seleccionada. 

DEVICE_CONN_AUD_DEV	Connect either the Optical (SPDIF) digital audio output or the L-R analog audio output from the HDTV to the audio input of your device.	Connectez soit l'optique (SPDIF) sortie audio numérique ou la sortie audio analogique LR de la TVHD à l'entrée audio de votre appareil.	Conecte a la salida de audio digital Optico (SPDIF) o a la LR salida de audio analogica de la television HDTV a la entrada de audio del dispositivo. 

DEVICE_CONN_AUD_CHG_VOLUME	Did the device change volume?	Did the device change volume?	Did the device change volume?

DEVICE_CONN_AUD_CTRL	"To start, aim your remote at the device, not the TV, and press the Volume Up or Down buttons."	"To start, aim your remote at the device, not the TV, and press the Volume Up or Down buttons."	"To start, aim your remote at the device, not the TV, and press the Volume Up or Down buttons."

DEVICE_VIA_CTRL	The remote control included with VIA can be used to control your 	La télécommande fournie avec VIA peuvent être utilisés pour contrôler votre	El control incluido con VIA puede ser usado para controlar su

DEVICE_POINT_REMOTE	"Point the remote at the device (not your TV), and push the %p Device-Power button, next to the Input button."	"Dirigez la télécommande vers l'appareil (et non votre TV), et appuyez sur le Device-bouton d'alimentation, à côté du bouton d'entrée."	"Apunte el control remoto al dispositivo (no al televisor), y oprima el boton de Encender Dispositivo, ubicado junto al boton de entrada. "

DEVICE_ATTEMP_CODESET	Attempting codeset 	Tenter de définir le code	Intentar juego de codigos. 

DEVICE_YES	Yes	Oui	Sí

DEVICE_START_AGAIN	"  No, Start Over Again"	"  Non, recommencer"	"No, Empezar Otra Vez"

DEVICE_TURN_OFF	Did the device turn off?	Ce que le dispositif de l'éteindre?	Se apago el dispositivo?

DEVICE_TRY_NEXT_CODE	"  No, Try The Next Code"	"  Non, essayez le code suivant"	"No, Intentar el proximo codigo"

DEVICE_MAN_ENTER_CODE	  Manually Enter Remote Code	  Entrée manuelle de code à distance	Manualmente entrar el codigo

DEVICE_RE_ENTER_CODE	"  No, Let Me Re-Enter the Code"	"  Non, laissez-moi réintroduisent le code"	"  No, volver entrar el codigo"

DEVICE_ENTER_CTRL_CODE	Enter the 3-digit remote control code:	Entrez le code de contrôle à distance à 3 chiffres:	Entrar el codigo de 3 digitos

DEVICE_ENTER_CODE	Enter Code	Entrez le code	Entrar codigo

DEVICE_NEXT	Next	Suivant	Siguiente

DEVICE_ADDI_DEVICE	Set Up An Additional Device	Configurer un périphérique supplémentaire	Configurar un dispositivo adicional

DEVICE_FINISH_SET_UP	Finished With Device Set Up	Fini avec dispositif mis en place	Acabar de configurar dispositivos

DEVICE_EXIT_PROMPT_DLG_TEXT	"If you do not set up your device(s), you will not be able to watch your favorite content or control them using the VIA remote. Are you sure you want to skip this step?"	"Si vous ne réglez pas votre appareil (s), vous ne serez pas en mesure de regarder votre contenu favori ou de les contrôler à distance en utilisant le VIA. Etes-vous sûr que vous voulez sauter cette étape?"	"Si no configura su/s dispos., no podra ver su contenido favorito o controlarlos usando el control VIA. Esta seguro que desea omitir este paso? "

DEVICE_SPEAKER_PROMPT_DLG_TEXT	This option will disable the TV speakers. Audio will be directed to your attached audio device.	Cette option permet de désactiver les enceintes du téléviseur. Audio seront dirigés vers votre appareil audio ci-joint.	Esta opcion desactivara las bocinas de la tele. El audio sera dirigira a su dispositivo conectado. 

LOC_DESC_TEXT_01	Insert the provided batteries into the remote control and use the UP 	Insérez les piles fournies dans la télécommande et d'utiliser le UP 	Coloque las baterías adjuntas en el control remoto y use los botones ARRIBA 

LOC_DESC_TEXT_02	", DOWN "	", BAS"	", ABAJO"

LOC_DESC_TEXT_03	 and OK buttons to navigate the set-up screens.	 et OK pour naviguer dans les écrans de paramétrage. 	 y ACEPTAR para navegar por las pantallas de configuración.

RETAIL_CONFIRM	"This is for retail display only and is not meant for home use, are you sure you want to enter the store demo mode?"	"Ceci est pour affichage en magasin seulement et n'est pas destiné à une utilisation à la maison, voulez-vous vraiment passer en mode de démonstration en magasin?"	"Esto es para exhibición en locales de venta únicamente y no está pensado para uso doméstico, ¿está seguro de que desea activar el modo de demostración para tiendas?"

TITLE_TV_SETUP	Set Up Your \nTV Signal 	Configuration \nsignal TV	Configurar señal \nde su TV

TV_SETUP_DESC	How are you receiving your TV service?	Comment recevez-vous la TV ?	¿Cómo recibe su servicio de TV?

NO_CH	No channels detected	Aucun canal détecté.	No se detectaron canales.

CH_DETECTED_01	Channels detected: 	Chaînes détectées : 	CANALES DETECTADOS:

CH_DETECTED_02	digital and	numériques et	digitales y

CH_DETECTED_03	 analog	analogiques	analógicos

CH_DETECTED_04	 channels	canaux.	canales.

SETUP_CMPL	Congratulations. Set up is complete!	Bravo. Configuration terminée !	¡Configuración Terminada!

TITLE_CMPL_VIZIO	Set Up\nComplete	Configuration\nterminée	Configuración\nTerminada

TUNER_SCANNING_TIP	VIA is now scanning all of the channels. This will take some time.	VIA effectue maintenant le balayage de tous les canaux. Cela peut durer un moment.	VIA está escaneando todos los canales. Puede tardarse un poco.

TUNER_CABLE_CONNECT	Select cable device	Choisissez le dispositif de câble	Elija dispositivo de cable

TUNER_CABLE_PROMPT_TEXT	"Do you have a cable box, or do you connect the cable from the wall directly to the TV?"	"Avez-vous une boîte de câble, ou reliez-vous le câble du mur directement à la TV ?"	"¿Tiene una caja de cable, o se puede conectar el cable de la pared directamente al televisor?"

TUNER_CABLE_BOX	Through a cable box	Par une décodeur	A traves de caja de cable

TUNER_CABLE_WALL	Direct from Wall	Direct du Mur	Directo de la Pared

TUNER_CABLE_INPUT_DEVICE	Select Input	sélection de l'entrée	Seleccionar Entrada

COUNTRY_CA	Canada	Canada	Canadá

COUNTRY_MEX	Mexico	Mexique 	México

COUNTRY_USA	USA	USA	EE.UU.

LANG_TITLE	Press OK to select language and country.	Appuyez sur OK pour sélectionner la langue et le pays.	Pulsar OK para seleccionar la lengua y país.

LANG	Language	Langue	Idioma

COUNTRY	Country	Pays	Pais

NETWORK_REG_INFO_POSTAL	Postal Code	Code postal	Código postal

CHO_MODE	Choose your mode. \n Select Store Demo for in-store display. \n Select Home Use for in-home use.	"Choisissez ""Home Use"" pour le Mode Domicile ou ""Store Demo"" pour la Démo en Magasin."	"Seleccione ""Home Use"" para Modo de Casa o ""Store Demo"" para Demostración en la Tienda."

SERVICE_CHECK_ITEM	Service Check	Service Check	Service Check

HELP_SERVICE_CHECK	"When requested by service personnel, performs a service check to verify the TV status."	"Quand demandé par le personnel de service, exécute un chèque de service pour vérifier le statut de TV."	"When requested by service personnel, performs a service check to verify the TV status."

SERVICE_CHECK_HELP_INFO	Do you want to perform a service check?	Voulez-vous exécuter un chèque de service ?	Quiere usted realizar un control de servicio?

NETWORK_ROUTER_LIST_WPS_ASSOCIATE	WPS	WPS	WPS

TV_REMOTE_BRAND_NAME_HINT_MSG	Type the first letters of the manufacturer's Brand Name. Then choose it from the drop-down menu.	Entrez les premières lettres du nom de la marque du fabricant. Choisissez ensuite ce nom dans le menu déroulant.	"Escriba la(s) primera(s) letra(s) del nombre de la marca del fabricante. Después, elija ese nombre del menú desplegable. "

TV_REMOTE_MODEL_NAME_HINT_MSG	Type the first letters of the manufacturer's Model Name. Then choose it from the drop-down menu.	Entrez les premières lettres du nom de la modèle du fabricant. Choisissez ensuite ce nom dans le menu déroulant.	"Escriba la(s) primera(s) letra(s) del nombre del modelo del fabricante. Después, elija ese nombre del menú desplegable. "

TV_REMOTE_BRAND_TITLE_BRAND	Brand	MARQUE	MARCA

TV_REMOTE_MODEL_TITLE_MODEL	Model	MODÈLE 	MODELO 

WZD_WPS_SETUP	Wi-Fi Protected Setup(WPS)\nPlease press the button on your router now	Wi-Fi Organisation Protégée (WPS)\nAppuyez s'il vous plaît sur le bouton sur votre détoureuse.	Configuración Protegida del Wi-Fi (WPS)\nPor favor presione el botón en su gestor de tráfico ahora.

SELECT_RESET	Select Reset to return settings to  factory defaults.	Choisissez Réinitialiser pour rendre des cadres défaut d'usine. 	Seleccione Reiniciar para regresar la TV a los Ajustes Originales.

LANG_TITLE_2	SELECT A LANGUAGE	SÉLECTIONNEZ UNE LANGUE	SELECCIONE UN IDIOMA

LANG_HELP	Press %p to use English as the primary language.	Appuyez sur %p pour utiliser le Français comme langue principale.	Presione %p para utilizar Español como idioma principal.

COUNTRY_TITLE	SELECT A COUNTRY	SÉLECTIONNEZ UN PAYS	SELECCIONE UN PAÍS

COUNTRY_HELP	Press %p to select the country.	Appuyez sur %p pour sélectionner le pays.	Presione %p para seleccionar el país.

COUNTRY_HELP_CAN	Press %p to select CANADA as your country.	Press %p to select CANADA as your country.	Press %p to select CANADA as your country.

COUNTRY_HELP_MEX	Press %p to select MEXICO as your country.	Press %p to select MEXICO as your country.	Press %p to select MEXICO as your country.

TITLE_NETWORK_SETUP	SELECT A NETWORK	SÉLECTIONNEZ UN RESEAU	SELECCIONE UNA RED

NW_SECURE_NONE	None	RIEN	NADA

NW_SECURE_WEP	WEP	WEP	WEP

NW_SECURE_WPA	WPA	WPA	WPA

NW_SECURE_WPA2	WPA2	WPA2	WPA2

NW_SECURE_WPA_ENTERPRISE	WPA \nEnterprise	WPA \nEnterprise	WPA \nEnterprise

NW_SECURE_WPA2_ENTERPRISE	WPA2 \nEnterprise	WPA2 \nEnterprise	WPA2 \nEnterprise

NW_SECURE_WEP_ENTERPRISE	WEP \nEnterprise	WEP \nEnterprise	WEP \nEnterprise

DEVICE_SETUP_SETUP_TITLE	DEVICE SETUP	INSTALLATION DE L'APPAREIL	PROGRAMACIÓN DEL  APARATO

DEVICE_SETUP_INPUT_TITLE	DEVICE INPUT	ENTRÉE DE L'APPAREIL 	ENTRADA DE APARATO

DEVICE_SETUP_BRAND_TITLE	BRAND	MARQUE	MARCA

DEVICE_SETUP_MODEL_TITLE	MODEL	MODÈLE 	MODELO 

DEVICE_SETUP_CONFIRM_TITLE	CONFIRM REMOTE CONNECTION	CONFIRMEZ LA CONNEXION DE TÉLÉCOMMANDE	CONFIRME CONEXIÓN DE CONTROL REMOTO

DEVICE_SETUP_SEL_TYPE_MSG	Select the type of device you want to set up.	Sélectionnez le type d'appareil que vous voulez installer.	Seleccionar el tipo de aparato que desea programar.

DEVICE_SETUP_SEL_INPUT_MSG	Select the input connected to the 	Sélectionner l'entrée connectée au 	Seleccione la entrada conectada con el 

DEVICE_SETUP_SEL_INPUT_MSG_CABLE	Select the input connected to the Cable Box.	Sélectionner l’entrée connectée au Decodeur.	Seleccione la entrada conectada con la Caja de Cable.

DEVICE_SETUP_SEL_INPUT_MSG_SAT	Select the input connected to the Satellite. 	Sélectionner l’entrée connectée au Satellite.	Seleccione la entrada conectada con el Satélite.

DEVICE_SETUP_ENTER_BRAND_MSG	Enter the brand for the 	Entrez la marque du 	Programar la marca de 

DEVICE_SETUP_ENTER_BRAND_TIP	"Type the first letter(s) of the Manufacturer's brand name. Then, choose that name from the drop-down menu."	Tapez la (les) première(s) lettre(s) de la marque du fabricant. Ensuite sélectionnez son nom dans le menu déroulant.	"Teclear la primera letra(s) de el nombre de la marca del fabricante. Después, escoger ese nombre del menu desplegable."

DEVICE_SETUP_ENTER_MODEL_MSG	Enter the model for the 	Entrez le modèle du 	Programar el modelo de 

DEVICE_SETUP_ENTER_MODEL_TIP	"Type the first letter(s) of the Model Number.Then, choose that name from the drop-down menu.\n If unknown, choose the ""I Don't Know the Model"" button."	"Tapez la (les) première(s) lettre(s) du Numéro du Modèle. Ensuite sélectionnez son nom dans le menu déroulant.\nSi vous ne connaissez pas le modèle, choisissez le bouton ""Je ne Connais pas le Modèle"""	"Teclear la primera letra(s) del modelo. Después, escoger ese nombre del menu desplegable.\n Si no lo sabe, escoja el botón ""No se el modelo""."

DEVICE_SETUP_CONFIRM_CONNECT	Attempting to connect to 	Tentative de connexion au  	Intentando conectarse a 

DEVICE_SETUP_CONFIRM_HTXT_MIG	"Point the remote at your device (not your TV), and press the "	"Dirigez la télécommande vers l'appareil (pas votre TV), et appuyez sur la"	"Apunte el control remote al dispositivo (no al televisor), y oprima el"

DEVICE_SETUP_CONFIRM_HTXT_MIG_APPEND	Device Power key %p next to the input key.	"touche d'Alimentation de l'Appareil %p , située à côté de la touche d'entrée.  "	"botón de Encender Dispositivo %p, ubicado junto al boton de input. "

DEVICE_SETUP_CONFIRM_AUDIO_DEV_MIG	"Point the remote at your device (not your TV), and press the\nvolume up and down keys."	"Dirigez la télécommande vers l'appareil (pas votre TV), et appuyez sur les touches volume haut et volume bas."	"Apunte el control remoto al dispositivo (no al televisor), y oprima los botones del\n volumen arriba or volumen abajo."

DEVICE_SETUP_CODESET_NOT_FOUND	The code was not found.	Le code n'a pas été trouvé.	El código no fue encontrado.

DEVICE_SETUP_CONFIRM_CODE_MSG	Remote Code 	Code de Télécommande 	Código de Remoto 

DEVICE_SETUP_CONFIRM_CODE_MSG_APPEND	 of 	 de 	 de 

DEVICE_SETUP_COMPLETE_TIP	Your 	Votre 	Su 

DEVICE_SETUP_COMPLETE_MIG	is set up.	est configuré.	esta programada.

DEVICE_SETUP_COMPLETE_MIG_AUD	 TV Speakers turned off.	 TV Speakers turned off.	 TV Speakers turned off.

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_BLU_RAY	Blu-ray	Blu-ray	Blu-ray

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_CABLE_BOX	Cable Box	Décodeur	Caja de Cable

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_COMPUTER	Computer	Ordinateur	Computadora

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_DVD_PLAYER	DVD	DVD	DVD

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_DVR	DVR	DVR	DVR

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_GAME	Game	Jeu	Juego

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_SATELLITE	Satellite	Satellite	Satélite

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_VCR	VCR	VCR	VCR

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_AUDIO_RECIEVER	Audio Receiver\n/Amplifier	Récepteur Audio\n/Amplificateur	Receptor Audio\n/Amplificador

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_SOUND_BAR	Sound Bar	Barre de Son	Barra de Sonido

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_AVR_AUDIO_RECEIVER	Audio Receiver	Récepteur Audio	Receptor Audio

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_AVR_AMP	Amplifier	Amp	Amp

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_BLU_RAY_MSG	Blu-ray.	Blu-ray.	Blu-ray.

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_CABLE_BOX_MSG	Cable Box.	Decodeur.	Caja de Cable.

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_COMPUTER_MSG	Computer.	Ordinateur.	Computadora.

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_DVD_PLAYER_MSG	DVD.	DVD.	DVD.

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_DVR_MSG	DVR.	DVR.	DVR.

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_GAME_MSG	Game.	Jeu.	Juego.

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_SATELLITE_MSG	Satellite.	Satellite.	Satélite.

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_VCR_MSG	VCR.	VCR.	VCR.

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_AUDIO_RECIEVER_MSG	Audio Receiver/Amplifier.	Récepteur Audio/Amplificateur.	Receptor Audio/Amplificador.

DEVICE_SETUP_TYPE_SOUND_BAR_MSG	Sound Bar.	Barre de Son.	Barra de Sonido.

DEVICE_SETUP_BTN_FINISHED	Finished	Terminé	Terminado

DEVICE_SETUP_BTN_BACK	Back	Retour	Atrás

DEVICE_SETUP_BTN_NEXT	Next	Suivant	Siguiente

DEVICE_SETUP_BTN_SKIP	Skip	Passer	Omitir

DEVICE_SETUP_BTN_IT_WORKED	 turned off	 Éteint	 Apagado

DEVICE_SETUP_BTN_AVR_IT_WORKED	Volume Has Changed	Volume Has Changed	Volume Has Changed

DEVICE_SETUP_BTN_TURNED_OFF	 Turned Off	  Éteint	  se apagar

DEVICE_SETUP_BTN_MANU_ENTER_CODE	Manually Enter the Code	Entrée Manuelle du Code	Manualmente Entrar el Código

DEVICE_SETUP_DLG_MANU_ENTER_CODE_TITLE	Enter the four digit code.	Entrer les quatre chiffres du code.	Ingrese el código de cuatro dígitos.

DEVICE_SETUP_BTN_TRY_THE_NEXT_CODE	Try the Next Code	Essayez le Code Suivant	Intentar el Proximo Código

DEVICE_SETUP_BTN_UNKNOWN_MODEL	I Don't Know the Model	Je ne Connais pas le Modèle	No Se el Modelo

DEVICE_SETUP_FINISHED_IMG	Setup is complete.	Configuration est terminé.	Programación está completa.

TV_DEVICE_NAME_INPUT_TITLE	NAME INPUT	SAISIR LE NOM	NOMBRE LA ENTRADA

TV_DEVICE_NAME_INPUT_CABLE_BOX_TITLE	CABLE BOX INPUT	ENTRÉE DU DECODEUR	ENTRADA DE CAJA DE CABLE

TV_DEVICE_NAME_INPUT_SATELLITE_TITLE	SATELLITE INPUT	ENTRÉE DU SATELLITE	ENTRADA DE SATÉLITE

TV_DEVICE_NAME_INPUT_SELECT_TYPE_MSG	Name an input from a set of common device names.	Nommez une entrée à partir d'une série de noms d'appareils communs.	Asigne un nombre a la entrada de un conjunto de nombres comunes de dispositivos.

TV_DEVICE_NAME_INPUT_SELECT_SRC_MSG	Select the input connected to the 	Sélectionner l'entrée connectée au 	Seleccione la entrada conectada con el 

TV_DEVICE_NAME_INPUT_DLG_MSG_1			Cambiar el nombre para\n 

TV_DEVICE_NAME_INPUT_DLG_MSG_2	 renamed to\n	 renommé en\n	 a 

TV_SETUP_TV_SIGNAL	TV SIGNAL	SIGNAL TV	SEÑAL DE TV 

TV_SETUP_DESC_TXT1	Select how you watch TV.	Sélectionnez le mode avec lequel vous allez regarder la télévision.	Seleccione cómo ver TV.

TV_SETUP_DESC_TXT2	You can control all your devices with the VIZIO remote.	Vous pouvez contrôler tous vos appareils avec la télécommande VIZIO.	Usted puede controlar todos sus aparatos con el control remoto VIZIO.

TV_SETUP_CABLE_CONNECT_WAY	How is your cable connected?	Comment le câble est-il connecté ?	¿Cómo está conectada su señal de cable?

TV_SETUP_AND	digital and	numériques et	digitales y

TV_SETUP_CHANNEL_DETECTED	CHANNELS DETECTED:	CHAÎNES DÉTECTÉES:	CANALES DETECTADOS:

TV_SETUP_ANALOG	analog	analogiques	analógicos

TV_SETUP_SKIP_DIG	If you skip TV setup you can not change channels with the VIZIO remote.	"Si vous ne configurez pas la TV, vous ne pourrez pas changer de chaînes avec la télécommande VIZIO."	Si omite la programación de TV no podrá cambiar de canal con el control remoto VIZIO.

TV_SETUP_SKIP_DIG_DESC	You can set up the antenna or TV device later in the Settings menu.	Vous pourrez configurer l'antenne ou la TV plus tard dans le menu des Paramètres.	"Puede programar la antena o el aparato de TV después, usando el menú de Programación."

TV_SETUP_SKIP_BUTTON1	Skip TV Setup	Evitez la Configuration	Omitir Programación  de TV

TV_SETUP_SKIP_BUTTON2	Back	Retour	Atrás

POWER_OFF_WARNING	Press the small white power button next to the input key.	Appuyez sur le petit bouton blanc d'alimentation situé à côté de la touche d'entrée. 	Oprima el pequeño botón blanco junto a la tecla de entrada.

NW_SETUP_CONNECTING_TO	Connecting to 	Connexion au 	Conectando a 

NW_SETUP_CONNECTING_ETHERNET	Connecting Ethernet	Connexion Ethernet	Conectando Ethernet

NW_SETUP_CONNECTING_WPS	Connecting WPS	Connexion WPS	Conectando WPS

NW_SETUP_CONNECTING_NETWORK	Connecting to Network	Connexion au Réseau	Conectando a la Red

NW_SETUP_CONNECTED_TO	Connected to \n	Connecté à \n	Conectado a \n

NW_SETUP_CONNECTED_TO_ETHERNET	Ethernet Connected	Ethernet Connecté	Ethernet Conectado

NW_SETUP_CONNECTED_TO_WPS	WPS Connected	WPS Connecté	WPS Conectado

NW_SETUP_CONNECTED_TO_NETWORK	Connected to the Network	Connecté à Réseau	Conectado a  la Red

NW_SETUP_MAC_ADDRESS	MAC Address: 	Adresse de MAC: 	Dirección MAC: 

NW_SETUP_NO_NETWORK_FOUND	No Networks Found	Aucun Réseau Trouvé	Ninguna Red Encontrada 

NW_SETUP_LOOKING_NETWORK	Looking for Networks…	Recherche des Réseaux…	Buscando Redes…

NW_SETUP_LOOKING_NETWORK_2	Looking for \nNetworks…	Recherche des  \nRéseaux…	Buscando \nRedes…   

NW_SETUP_TITLE_TOS_AND_POLICY	TERMS OF SERVICE	CONDITIONS D'UTILISATION	TÉRMINOS DE SERVICIO

NW_SETUP_TITLE_TOS	TERMS AND CONDITIONS	CONDITIONS ET LIMITES	CONDICIONES Y TÉRMINOS

NW_SETUP_TITLE_POLICY	PRIVACY POLICY	PROTECTION DE LA VIE PRIVÉE	POLITICA DE PRIVACIDAD

NW_SETUP_BTN_TOS	Terms and Conditions	Conditions et Limites	Condiciones y Términos

NW_SETUP_BTN_POLICY	Privacy Policy	Protection de la Vie Privée	Politica de Privacidad

NW_SETUP_TERMS_DOWNLOAD_FAILED	View the Yahoo! TV Widget System Terms of Service at:\nhttps://info.yahoo.com/legal/us/yahoo/connectedtv/tos.html	View the Yahoo! TV Widget System Terms of Service at:\nhttps://info.yahoo.com/legal/us/yahoo/connectedtv/tos.html	Ver los Términos  de Servicio de Yahoo! Connected TV en:\nhttps://info.yahoo.com/legal/us/yahoo/connectedtv/tos.html

NW_SETUP_POLICY_DOWNLOAD_FAILED	View the Yahoo! TV Widget System Privacy Policy at:\nhttps://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/connectedtv/	View the Yahoo! TV Widget System Privacy Policy at:\nhttps://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/connectedtv/	Ver la Política de Privacidad de Yahoo! Connected TV en:\nhttps://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/connectedtv/

NW_SETUP_FOOTER_HIDE_NETWORK	Hidden Network	Réseau Masqué	Red Escondida

NW_SETUP_FOOTER_TRY_AGAIN	Try Again	Veuillez Réessayer	Intente de Nuevo

NW_SETUP_FOOTER_TRY_ANOTHER_NW	Try Another Network	Veuillez un Autre Réseau	Intente Otra Red

NW_SETUP_FOOTER_SKIP	Skip	Passer	Omitir

NW_SETUP_FOOTER_CANCEL	Cancel	Annulez	Cancelar

NW_SETUP_FOOTER_NEXT	Next	Suivant	Siguiente

NW_SETUP_FOOTER_CONNECT	Connect	Connecter	Conectar

NW_SETUP_FOOTER_WPS	WPS	WPS	WPS

NW_SETUP_FOOTER_ACCEPT	I Accept	J'accepte	Acepto

NW_SETUP_FOOTER_DECLINE	Decline	Décliner	Niego

NW_SETUP_WPS_CONN	Wi-Fi Protected Setup	Installation Wi-Fi Protégée (WPS)	Configuración Protegida del Wi-Fi (WPS)

NW_SETUP_WPS_CONN_DESC	Press the WPS button on your home router now.	Appuyez sur le bouton WPS de votre routeur maintenant.	Presione el botón de WPS en su gestor de tráfico de casa ahora.

NW_SETUP_WPS_CONN_FAIL	Unable to connect WPS	Impossible de se connecter WPS	No se pudo establecer la conexión WPS

NW_SETUP_NETWORK_CONN_FAIL	Unable to connect the Network	Impossible de connecter	No se puede conectar

NW_SETUP_UNABLE_JOIN	Unable to connect to 	Impossible de se connecter à 	No se puede conectar al 

NW_SETUP_PW_INPUT	Enter the password for 	Entrez le Mot de Passe pour 	Ingrese la contraseña para 

NW_SETUP_PROMPT_PW_INPUT	Enter Password	Entrez le Mot de Passe	Ingrese Contraseña

NW_SETUP_SSID_INPUT	Enter the name for Hidden Network	Entrez le nom du Réseau Masqué	Ingrese el nombre de Red Escondida

NW_SETUP_PROMPT_SSID_INPUT	Enter SSID	Entrez SSID	Ingrese SSID

TIME_ZONE_SETUP_TITLE	TIME ZONE	FUSEAU HORAIRE	ZONA HORARIA

TIME_ZONE_SETUP_DESC	Select your time zone.	Sélectionnez votre fuseau horaire.	Seleccione la zona horaria.

TIME_ZONE_SETUP_BTN_OTHER_TZ	Other Time Zones	D'Autre Fuseau Horaire	Otra Zona Horaria

TIME_ZONE_SETUP_DLG_DESC	Use the number keys to enter the UTC offset for your time zone \n(-12 to 12).	Utilisez les touches numériques pour saisir le décalage UTC pour votre fuseau horaire (-12 à 12).	Use las teclas numéricas para ingresar el cambio de UTC según su zona horaria (-12 a 12).

TIME_ZONE_SETUP_INVALID_OFFSET	Invalid. Try again.  	Invalide.  Veuillez réessayer.	Inválido. Intente de nuevo. 

TUNER_SETUP_STOP_SCAN_MSG	"Channel Scan is not completed, not all channels are found. "	"Le balayage des chaînes n'est pas terminée, pas toutes les chaînes sont trouvées. "	"Escaneo de canales no es completada, no todos los canales son encontrados."

TUNER_SETUP_STOP_SCAN	Stop Scan	Arrêtez le Balayage	Detenga la Búsqueda

TUNER_SETUP_CONTINUE_SCAN	Continue Scan	Continuez le Balayage	Continuar la Búsqueda

